好 首先我们打开教师笔记(instructor notes)
All right, so first we load up the webpage that was linked
里面的网站
in the instructor notes.
我们可以看到里面已经有了和 Happy Birthday TextView
We see that it's populated already with some code for
相关的代码
the Happy Birthday TextView.
在右侧 我们可以看见设备及其预览
And then on the right, we see the preview and the device.
为了改变出现在那里的文字
To change the text that appears here,
我们就要改变 Android:text 的属性值
we need to change the value of the attribute called Android:text.
因此在引号里面 我们就可以更改文字
So in between the quotes here we can change the message.
比如说 改成 Happy Birthday to my pet hamster!
Can change it to, hm, Happy Birthday to my pet hamster!
然后在设备上 我们可以看见文字已经被更新了 喔嚄！
Then on the device, we can see that the text has now been updated, woohoo!
为改变 view 的尺寸 我们可以改变
To change the size of the view, we can modify the width and
宽度(width)和高度(height)的属性值
height attribute values.
在引号里面 我们删掉原来的
The in between quotations, we can delete that and
并且改成诸如 250dp 的东西
change it to something like 250dp.
至于高度 我们可以修改为 450dp
And then for the height we can change it to like 450dp.
现在 我们可以看见 灰色背景的 text view 大一点了
And now, we see that the text view with the gray background is now a lot bigger.
酷
Cool.
最后的问题是 制造一个错误
So, the last part of the quiz was to try to create an error.
如果我删掉这个斜杠和这个括号
So, if I delete the forward slash and the angle bracket, then,
那么我就会在底下得到一堆错误
I get a bunch of errors that show up on the bottom, here.
而且 设备预览也会变灰
Also, the device greys out,
因为没有可以用来显示的正确预览
because there's no valid preview to show on the device anymore.
这些错误可以帮助你修正你的代码 而且因为我们知道我们需要做什么来修正
These errors can help you fix your code, and since we know what
我们就简单地按一下 Ctrl+Z 来撤销我们的更改
we need to do to fix it, we can just hit Ctrl+Z to undo the changes we made.
这个快捷键很常用 在 Mac 上面是 Cmd+Z
The undo shortcut is really useful to use, so it's Cmd+Z on a Mac,
在 Windows 上面是 Ctrl+Z
or Ctrl+Z on a Windows.
我们也可以制造其他错误 比如删除引号
We can create other errors as well, such as deleting a quotation mark and
我们就可以在下面看到错误
we see the error down here.
同样我们可以撤销 使之恢复原样
We can hit undo to make it come back.
我们也可以把 darker grey 换成 parker grey
Or we can change darker grey to parker grey,
显然 Android 不认识这种颜色
which apparently Android doesn't recognize, unfortunately.
我们就可以转换回来
So we can just switch it back.